Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/kenneth-ho-88461424 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Audit

Security

Compliance

Certifications

Certified Ethical Hacker v5 (CEH)

APMG Accredited Trainer - CSX Cybersecurity Fundamentals

Cybersecurity Fundamentals Certificate

Certified Information Security Manager® (CISM)

Certified Information Systems Auditor® (CISA)

Kenneth Ho

Vice President Information Technology Security Kuala Lumpur

Summary

A prominent cybersecurity expert with over 20 years of experience in enterprise IT services for the retail, blue chip multinational, investment banking, and professional services industries. An established, knowledgeable professional with past training experience in various enterprise IT domains including cloud computing and virtualisation. A two-term President of the Malaysian chapter of the international professional association focused on IT governance, Information Systems Audit and Control Association (ISACA) from 2016-2018.

Experience

CGS-CIMB Securities Malaysia
Vice President Information Technology Security
August 2021 - Present (5 months)
Kuala Lumpur, Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Maybank Kim Eng Regional Head, IT Security March 2016 - August 2021 (5 years 6 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

EY

Director, Cybersecurity
August 2015 - March 2016 (8 months)

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Maybank Investment Bank Berhad Head, Regional IT Security, Risk and Compliance June 2010 - August 2015 (5 years 3 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Jardine Matheson
IT Senior Consultant, Group Audit

September 2005 - June 2010 (4 years 10 months)

The Dairy Farm Group IT Senior Auditor June 2001 - September 2005 (4 years 4 months)

Carrefour IT Executive March 1999 - June 2001 (2 years 4 months)

Education

Griffith University
Information Technology, Information Systems, Software
Engineering · (1996 - 1998)